Finding Aid for the Delbert Mann Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- Productions
  - Productions Directed by Delbert Mann
    - Breaking Up, 1976 (Released 2 January 1978); Scripts Character List Cast Lists Titles Crew Lists Notes Music Notes Scene Lists Dialogue Post Sync Sound Effects List Schedules Production Plans Daily Production Reports Daily Reports Set Lists Location and Set Breakdown Wardrobe List Location Information Contact Lists Budget Broadcast Standards and Practices Reviews Publicity Correspondence (Box 40)
    - Tell Me My Name, 20 December 1977; Scripts Cast Lists Titles Notes Music Notes Effects Notes Background Scene and Timing Breakdown Dialogue Post Sync Program Format Schedules Production Plans Daily Production Reports Daily Reports Set Designs Wardrobe Notes Mock Newspaper Location Information Locations List Location Survey Summary Legal Documents Correspondence (Box 41)
    - Tell Me My Name, 20 December 1977; Scripts Cast Lists Titles Notes Music Notes Effects Notes Background Scene and Timing Breakdown Dialogue Post Sync Program Format Schedules Production Plans Daily Production Reports Daily Reports Set Designs Wardrobe Notes Mock Newspaper Location Information Locations List Location Survey Summary Legal Documents Correspondence (Box 42)
    - Home to Stay, 1977 (Released 2 May 1978); Scripts Cast Lists Crew Lists Credits Contact List Notes Music Notes Sound Notes Sound Effects Notes Set, Scene, and Location Breakdown Act and Timing Breakdown Story Time Sequence Second Unit Shots List Program Format Schedules Production Plans Daily Production Reports Daily and Continuity Reports Set Designs Set List Prop List Cars and Animals List Location Lists Location Survey Location Information Location Breakdown Location Photographs Publicity Correspondence (Box 42)
    - Home to Stay, 1977 (Released 2 May 1978); Scripts Cast Lists Crew Lists Credits Contact List Notes Music Notes Sound Notes Sound Effects Notes Set, Scene, and Location Breakdown Act and Timing Breakdown Story Time Sequence Second Unit Shots List Program Format Schedules Production Plans Daily Production Reports Daily and Continuity Reports Set Designs Set List Prop List Cars and Animals List Location Lists Location Survey Location Information Location Breakdown Location Photographs Publicity Correspondence (Box 43)
    - Love’s Dark Ride, 1977 (Released January 1978); Script Report Scripts Dialogue Replacement Credits Notes Music Notes Sound Effect Notes Scene, Location, and Actor Breakdown Assistant Directors Breakdown Sheets (Scene and Actor Breakdown) Story Time Sequence Program Format Schedules Daily Production Reports Location Information Broadcast Standards Acceptability Report Correspondence (Box 43)
    - Love’s Dark Ride, 1977 (Released January 1978); Script Report Scripts Dialogue Replacement Credits Notes Music Notes Sound Effect Notes Scene, Location, and Actor Breakdown Assistant Directors Breakdown Sheets (Scene and Actor Breakdown) Story Time Sequence Program Format Schedules Daily Production Reports Location Information Broadcast Standards Acceptability Report Correspondence (Box 44)
    - Tom and Joann, 1978; Scripts Title Sequence Credits Notes Music Notes Sound Notes Schedules Production Plans Daily Production Reports Set Breakdown Location Information Location Breakdown Location Photographs Broadcast Standards Review Correspondence (Box 44)
    - Thou Shalt Not Commit Adultery, 1 November 1978; Scripts Script Revisions Crew Lists Credits Notes Music Notes Scene and Timing Breakdown Program Format Schedules Production Book Daily Production Reports Actors Daily Time Reports Set Designs Wardrobe Lists Location Information Budget Legal Research Legal Documents Broadcast Standards and Acceptability Report Ratings Report Correspondence (Box 44)
    - Thou Shalt Not Commit Adultery, 1 November 1978; Scripts Script Revisions Crew Lists Credits Notes Music Notes Scene and Timing Breakdown Program Format Schedules Production Book Daily Production Reports Actors Daily Time Reports Set Designs Wardrobe Lists Location Information Budget Legal Research Legal Documents Broadcast Standards and Acceptability Report Ratings Report Correspondence (Box 45)
    - Thou Shalt Not Commit Adultery, 1 November 1978; Scripts Script Revisions Crew Lists Credits Notes Music Notes Scene and Timing Breakdown Program Format Schedules Production Book Daily Production Reports Actors Daily Time Reports Set Designs Wardrobe Lists Location Information Budget Legal Research Legal Documents Broadcast Standards and Acceptability Report Ratings Report Correspondence (Box 46)
    - Roots II: The Next Generation, 1978 (brief segment), Script Scene, Set and Actor Breakdown Schedules (Box 46)
    - Torn Between Two Lovers, 1979; Scripts Looping and Wild Lines Cast and Crew Lists Notes Music Notes Program Format Schedules Production Plans Daily Production Reports Set Design Location and Set List Wardrobe Notes Location Information Legal Research Notice Correspondence (Box 46)
    - Torn Between Two Lovers, 1979; Scripts Looping and Wild Lines Cast and Crew Lists Notes Music Notes Program Format Schedules Production Plans Daily Production Reports Set Design Location and Set List Wardrobe Notes Location Information Legal Research Notice Correspondence (Box 47)
    - All Quiet on the Western Front, 14 November 1979; Outlines Scripts Narration Cast Lists Crew Lists Credits Contact List Notes Music Notes Sound Notes Background Scene and Timing Breakdown Scene Lists Time Sequence List of Suggested Cuts Program Format Schedules Daily Progress Reports Daily Diary Set Designs Sketches Location and Set List Costume and Make-up Breakdown Prop Lists Location Information Broadcast Standards Reviews Publicity Correspondence (Box 47)
    - All Quiet on the Western Front, 14 November 1979; Outlines Scripts Narration Cast Lists Crew Lists Credits Contact List Notes Music Notes Sound Notes Background Scene and Timing Breakdown Scene Lists Time Sequence List of Suggested Cuts Program Format Schedules Daily Progress Reports Daily Diary Set Designs Sketches Location and Set List Costume and Make-up Breakdown Prop Lists Location Information Broadcast Standards Reviews Publicity Correspondence (Box 48)
    - To Find My Son, September 1980; Scripts Cast Lists Crew Lists Notes Story Continuity outline Dialogue Replacement List of Wild Tracks Recorded Lyrics Schedules Daily Reports Set Lists Set Designs Location Information Location Photographs Notices Correspondence (Box 48)
    - To Find My Son, September 1980; Scripts Cast Lists Crew Lists Notes Story Continuity outline Dialogue Replacement List of Wild Tracks Recorded Lyrics Schedules Daily Reports Set Lists Set Designs Location Information Location Photographs Notices Correspondence (Box 49)
    - Night Crossing, 1980; Script Report Scripts Narration Cast Lists Notes Music Notes Background Scene and Timing Breakdown Loops and Wild Lines Post-Production Shots List Second Unit Shots Lists Lists of Plates Needed Schedules Production Plans Daily Production Reports Location and Set Lists Location Information Budget Legal Research Ratings Report Notices Correspondence (Box 49)
    - Night Crossing, 1980; Script Report Scripts Narration Cast Lists Notes Music Notes Background Scene and Timing Breakdown Loops and Wild Lines Post-Production Shots List Second Unit Shots Lists Lists of Plates Needed Schedules Production Plans Daily Production Reports Location and Set Lists Location Information Budget Legal Research Ratings Report Notices Correspondence (Box 50)
    - Night Crossing, 1980; Script Report Scripts Narration Cast Lists Notes Music Notes Background Scene and Timing Breakdown Loops and Wild Lines Post-Production Shots List Second Unit Shots Lists Lists of Plates Needed Schedules Production Plans Daily Production Reports Location and Set Lists Location Information Budget Legal Research Ratings Report Notices Correspondence (Box 51)
    - God’s Guerillas, 1981; Script Correspondence (Box 51)
    - All the Way Home, 21 December 1981; Scripts Cast Lists Casting Photograph Crew List Contact List Notes Background Scene and Timing Breakdown Program Format Schedules Budget Program Correspondence (Box 52)
    - Bronte, 1982; Script Reports Script Crew List Notes Music Notes Sound Notes Background Schedules Set Designs Prop List Agreement Correspondence (Box 52)
    - The Member of the Wedding, 20 December 1982; Scripts Cast Lists Crew Lists Notes Background Scene and Actor Breakdown Rehearsal Scene Structure Program Format Sheet Music Schedules Floor Plans Budget Publicity Correspondence (Box 52)
    - The Member of the Wedding, 20 December 1982; Scripts Cast Lists Crew Lists Notes Background Scene and Actor Breakdown Rehearsal Scene Structure Program Format Sheet Music Schedules Floor Plans Budget Publicity Correspondence (Box 53)
    - The Gift of Love, 1983; Script Cast Lists Crew Lists Notes Music Notes Sound Notes Scene and Timing Breakdown Scene Changes and Additions Program Format Schedules Daily Production Reports Location Information Publicity Notices Correspondence (Box 53)
    - Love Leads the Way, 1984; Script Reports Scripts Proposed Script Revisions Cast and Crew Lists Credits Character Descriptions Notes Background Time Sequence Schedules Daily Production Reports Location List Location Information Location Photographs Budget Notices Correspondence (Box 54)
    - Love Leads the Way, 1984; Script Reports Scripts Proposed Script Revisions Cast and Crew Lists Credits Character Descriptions Notes Background Time Sequence Schedules Daily Production Reports Location List Location Information Location Photographs Budget Notices Correspondence (Box 55)
    - A Death in California, May 1985; Script Report Scripts Dialogue Replacement Cast Lists Crew List Credits Character Descriptions Notes Effects Notes Music Notes Background Continuity Day Breakdown Program Format Schedules Production Plans Daily Production Reports Location Lists Location Information Location Photographs Budget ABC Credit Policy Broadcast Standards and Practices Reviews Publicity Correspondence (Box 55)
    - A Death in California, May 1985; Script Report Scripts Dialogue Replacement Cast Lists Crew List Credits Character Descriptions Notes Effects Notes Music Notes Background Continuity Day Breakdown Program Format Schedules Production Plans Daily Production Reports Location Lists Location Information Location Photographs Budget ABC Credit Policy Broadcast Standards and Practices Reviews Publicity Correspondence (Box 56)
    - A Death in California, May 1985; Script Report Scripts Dialogue Replacement Cast Lists Crew List Credits Character Descriptions Notes Effects Notes Music Notes Background Continuity Day Breakdown Program Format Schedules Production Plans Daily Production Reports Location Lists Location Information Location Photographs Budget ABC Credit Policy Broadcast Standards and Practices Reviews Publicity Correspondence (Box 57)
    - The Last Days of Patton, 1985 (Released 14 September 1986); Script Report Scripts Script Revisions Dialogue Replacement Cast List Contact Lists Credits Notes Music Notes Background Script Breakdown Act Breakdown Scene and Actor Breakdown Scene and Timing Breakdown Cast Breakdown Music Breakdown Filming Plans Action Drawings Program Format Schedules Production Plans Daily Production Reports Set List Set Designs Wardrobe List Action Vehicle List Budget Correspondence (Box 57)
    - The Last Days of Patton, 1985 (Released 14 September 1986); Script Report Scripts Script Revisions Dialogue Replacement Cast List Contact Lists Credits Notes Music Notes Background Script Breakdown Act Breakdown Scene and Actor Breakdown Scene and Timing Breakdown Cast Breakdown Music Breakdown Filming Plans Action Drawings Program Format Schedules Production Plans Daily Production Reports Set List Set Designs Wardrobe List Action Vehicle List Budget Correspondence (Box 58)
    - The Ted Kennedy, Jr., Story, 24 November 1986; Script Report Scripts Cast Lists Casting Notes Contact List Credits Notes Music Notes Scene and Set Breakdown Act and Timing Breakdown Cast Breakdown Program Format Technical Specifications NBC Film Program Delivery Requirements Sheet Music Lyrics Schedules Production Plans Daily Production Reports Set List Set Designs Location Information Correspondence (Box 59)
    - The Ted Kennedy, Jr., Story, 24 November 1986; Script Report Scripts Cast Lists Casting Notes Contact List Credits Notes Music Notes Scene and Set Breakdown Act and Timing Breakdown Cast Breakdown Program Format Technical Specifications NBC Film Program Delivery Requirements Sheet Music Lyrics Schedules Production Plans Daily Production Reports Set List Set Designs Location Information Correspondence (Box 60)
    - April Morning, 1987 (Released 24 April 1988) Papers, 1962-1973; Film Treatment Scripts Casting Notes Casting Photographs Character List Crew Notes Script Reports Notes Background Set List Budget Correspondence (Box 60)
    - April Morning, 1987 (Released 24 April 1988) Papers, 1962-1973; Film Treatment Scripts Casting Notes Casting Photographs Character List Crew Notes Script Reports Notes Background Set List Budget Correspondence (Box 61)
    - April Morning, 1987 (Released 24 April 1988) Papers, 1962-1973; Film Treatment Scripts Casting Notes Casting Photographs Character List Crew Notes Script Reports Notes Background Set List Budget Correspondence (Box 62)
    - April Morning, 1987 (Released 24 April 1988) Papers, 1962-1973; Film Treatment Scripts Casting Notes Casting Photographs Character List Crew Notes Script Reports Notes Background Set List Budget Correspondence (Box 63)
    - April Morning, 1987 (Released 24 April 1988) Papers, 1962-1973; Film Treatment Scripts Casting Notes Casting Photographs Character List Crew Notes Script Reports Notes Background Set List Budget Correspondence (Box 64)
    - April Morning, 1987 (Released 24 April 1988) Papers, 1981-1989; Scripts Lines for Opening Crawl Script Revisions Cast Lists Character Descriptions Crew Lists Credits CBS Credit Policy Notes Music Notes Background Scene Chronology Scene and Timing Breakdown Timing Report Cue Sheets Stunt Breakdown Sheet Music Technical Specifications Program Format Schedules Production Plans Daily Production Reports Progress Reports Makeup and Wardrobe Notes Location Breakdown Location information Location Photographs Budget Publicity Publicity Photographs Program Practices Review Reviews Cartoon Notices Correspondence (Box 60)
    - April Morning, 1987 (Released 24 April 1988) Papers, 1981-1989; Scripts Lines for Opening Crawl Script Revisions Cast Lists Character Descriptions Crew Lists Credits CBS Credit Policy Notes Music Notes Background Scene Chronology Scene and Timing Breakdown Timing Report Cue Sheets Stunt Breakdown Sheet Music Technical Specifications Program Format Schedules Production Plans Daily Production Reports Progress Reports Makeup and Wardrobe Notes Location Breakdown Location information Location Photographs Budget Publicity Publicity Photographs Program Practices Review Reviews Cartoon Notices Correspondence (Box 61)
    - April Morning, 1987 (Released 24 April 1988) Papers, 1981-1989; Scripts Lines for Opening Crawl Script Revisions Cast Lists Character Descriptions Crew Lists Credits CBS Credit Policy Notes Music Notes Background Scene Chronology Scene and Timing Breakdown Timing Report Cue Sheets Stunt Breakdown Sheet Music Technical Specifications Program Format Schedules Production Plans Daily Production Reports Progress Reports Makeup and Wardrobe Notes Location Breakdown Location information Location Photographs Budget Publicity Publicity Photographs Program Practices Review Reviews Cartoon Notices Correspondence (Box 62)
    - April Morning, 1987 (Released 24 April 1988) Papers, 1981-1989; Scripts Lines for Opening Crawl Script Revisions Cast Lists Character Descriptions Crew Lists Credits CBS Credit Policy Notes Music Notes Background Scene Chronology Scene and Timing Breakdown Timing Report Cue Sheets Stunt Breakdown Sheet Music Technical Specifications Program Format Schedules Production Plans Daily Production Reports Progress Reports Makeup and Wardrobe Notes Location Breakdown Location information Location Photographs Budget Publicity Publicity Photographs Program Practices Review Reviews Cartoon Notices Correspondence (Box 63)
    - April Morning, 1987 (Released 24 April 1988) Papers, 1981-1989; Scripts Lines for Opening Crawl Script Revisions Cast Lists Character Descriptions Crew Lists Credits CBS Credit Policy Notes Music Notes Background Scene Chronology Scene and Timing Breakdown Timing Report Cue Sheets Stunt Breakdown Sheet Music Technical Specifications Program Format Schedules Production Plans Daily Production Reports Progress Reports Makeup and Wardrobe Notes Location Breakdown Location information Location Photographs Budget Publicity Publicity Photographs Program Practices Review Reviews Cartoon Notices Correspondence (Box 64)
    - The Magnificent Yankee, May 1988; Cast Lists Background Program Publicity Correspondence (Box 64)
    - Stage 10, Live: The Petrified Forest, 7 September 1988; Script for Introduction Crew List Scene and Actor Breakdown Program Outline Schedule Set Designs Sketch Correspondence (Box 64)
    - The Memoirs of Abraham Lincoln, 20-21 April 1990, 28-29 October 1992; Script Report Scripts Script for Introduction Script Revisions Title Designs Production Proposal Notes Background Guidelines for Producing Performances Sound Cues Lighting Cues Edit List Camera Shot Lists Tape Log Sheet Music Lyrics Schedules Set Designs Sketches Prop Lists Location Information Location Photographs Budget Legal Document Programs Publicity Marketing Report Reviews Correspondence (Box 64)
    - The Memoirs of Abraham Lincoln, 20-21 April 1990, 28-29 October 1992; Script Report Scripts Script for Introduction Script Revisions Title Designs Production Proposal Notes Background Guidelines for Producing Performances Sound Cues Lighting Cues Edit List Camera Shot Lists Tape Log Sheet Music Lyrics Schedules Set Designs Sketches Prop Lists Location Information Location Photographs Budget Legal Document Programs Publicity Marketing Report Reviews Correspondence (Box 65)
    - Ironclads, 1990 (Released 11 March 1991); Scripts Dialogue Replacement Cast List Credits Credit Policy Notes Background Scene and Timing Breakdown Act Breaks Line Continuity Special Effects Breakdown Shot Lists Technical Requirements Music Notes Schedules Daily Production Reports Sketches Location Information Budget Legal Research Correspondence (Box 66)
    - Ironclads, 1990 (Released 11 March 1991); Scripts Dialogue Replacement Cast List Credits Credit Policy Notes Background Scene and Timing Breakdown Act Breaks Line Continuity Special Effects Breakdown Shot Lists Technical Requirements Music Notes Schedules Daily Production Reports Sketches Location Information Budget Legal Research Correspondence (Box 67)
    - Against Her Will: An Incident in Baltimore, 1991 (Released 19 January 1992); Scripts Dialogue Replacement Cast Lists Contact Lists Notes Background Act and Timing Breakdown Program Format Music Notes Music Scoring Schedules Daily Production Reports Set Designs Budget Legal Documents Legal Research Publicity Publicity Photographs Notices Correspondence (Box 68)
    - Against Her Will: An Incident in Baltimore, 1991 (Released 19 January 1992); Scripts Dialogue Replacement Cast Lists Contact Lists Notes Background Act and Timing Breakdown Program Format Music Notes Music Scoring Schedules Daily Production Reports Set Designs Budget Legal Documents Legal Research Publicity Publicity Photographs Notices Correspondence (Box 69)
  - Projects Not Completed
    - Spies for the Blue and Gray, 1957-1958; Scripts Notes Background Correspondence (Box 69)
    - Spies for the Blue and Gray, 1957-1958; Scripts Notes Background Correspondence (Box 70)
    - The Last Temptation, 1958; Notes Book Continuity Budget (Box 70)
    - To the Last Hour: The Oskar Schindler Story, 1965; Screenplay Treatment Character Descriptions Background Background Interviews Background Photographs Correspondence (Box 70)
    - Red Sky, 1965; Story Outline Scripts Character Descriptions Notes Correspondence (Box 70)
    - East Into the Sun, 1966-1968; Scripts Notes Correspondence (Box 71)
    - Rulers of Darkness, 1967-1968; Book Synopsis Notes Author List Set List Correspondence (Box 71)
    - Daniel Shays, 1968; Author List Budget Correspondence (Box 71)
    - Graduation at Gettysburg, 1968; Script Report Notes Background Legal Documents Correspondence (Box 71)
    - Vale Story, 1968; Cast Lists Notes Set List Correspondence (Box 71)
    - The Quaid, 1969; Casting Notes Background Correspondence (Box 71)
    - Little Women, 1970-1971; Treatment Book Synopsis Notes Publicity Correspondence (Box 71)
    - Plantagenet!, 1972-1973; Script Publicity Correspondence (Box 71)
    - Bring Along Laughter, 1973-1976; Outline Scripts Cast Lists Notes Photocopy of Original Book Correspondence (Box 72)
    - Fifty-Four Hours to Freedom, 1973; Treatment Notes Background Correspondence (Box 72)
    - The Last Time We Cried Like Children, 1973; Treatment Scripts Character List Set List Casting Notes Notes Background (Box 72)
    - The Last Time We Cried Like Children, 1973; Treatment Scripts Character List Set List Casting Notes Notes Background (Box 73)
    - The Brownsville Raid, 1973; Outline Notes Background Legal Document Correspondence (Box 73)
    - Kraft’s Most Unforgettable Characters, 1973; Outline Script Casting Notes Author Lists Notes Background Scene Breakdown Set List Correspondence (Box 73)
    - Crime Counsel, 1973-1976; Background Legal Document Correspondence (Box 73)
    - The Lees of Virginia, 1975; Treatment Scripts Character List Set List (Box 73)
    - The Lees of Virginia, 1975; Treatment Scripts Character List Set List (Box 74)
    - The Lees of Virginia, 1975; Treatment Scripts Character List Set List (Box 75)
    - Schweitzer’s Way, 1975-1976; Script Report Outline Scripts Casting Notes Notes Background Set List Correspondence (Box 76)
    - Schweitzer’s Way, 1975-1976; Script Report Outline Scripts Casting Notes Notes Background Set List Correspondence (Box 77)
    - Trinity, 1977; Outlines Scripts Character Lists Casting Notes Cast Lists Crew List Notes Background Scene Breakdown (Novel) Scene and Timing Breakdown Chronological Sequence Continuity Suggested Cuts Schedule Set List Location Information Correspondence (Box 77)
    - Trinity, 1977; Outlines Scripts Character Lists Casting Notes Cast Lists Crew List Notes Background Scene Breakdown (Novel) Scene and Timing Breakdown Chronological Sequence Continuity Suggested Cuts Schedule Set List Location Information Correspondence (Box 78)
    - A Measure of Time, 1978; Scripts Casting Notes Casting Photographs Crew List Contact List Notes Character Breakdown Schedules Production Plans Set Breakdown Set Designs Location Information Location Photographs Legal Document Correspondence (Box 79)
    - China Tiger, 1986; Script Report Script Notes (Box 80)
    - Dark of the Moon, undated, Script (Box 80)
    - Jubilee, undated, Script (Box 80)
    - Caruso, undated, Notes Background Location List Recording List (Box 80)
    - All I Said Was Love, 1969; Notes Correspondence (Box 80)
    - Cane, 1969; Correspondence (Box 80)
    - Don’t stop the Carnival, 1966; Treatment Notes Correspondence (Box 80)
    - Lew’s Girl, 1968-1972; Casting Notes Notes Correspondence (Box 80)
    - The Moonflower Vine, 1969; Correspondence (Box 80)
    - The Naked Weekend, 1966; Production Proposal Correspondence (Box 80)
    - Peer Gynt, undated, Production Proposal Casting Notes (Box 80)
    - The Royal Family, 1971; Correspondence (Box 80)
    - Souvenir of Geneva, 1967-1968; Casting Notes Correspondence (Box 80)